Boss.
Where are the brothers who left?
Tell them to come back quickly.
They've gone with the toll.
Oh no.
Boss.
Didn’t you allow them to leave?
It's hard to explain.
Let's go and stop them.
Don't shoot!
Ms. Huo.
What's wrong?
Boss.
Qinglong Fortress was occupied by demons.
and killed many people.
What?
This...
You may leave.
Yes.
This is my spy.
Bao, Uncle Erbai.
Qinglong Fortress is my home.
My father is gone now.
But there are villagers and people there.
We can't leave them alone.
Of course.
This...
Eagle, you're right.
We can't leave him alone.
But Master He and Zheng Xiong
colluded with each other
sooner or later
sooner or later.
The Black Tiger Mountain and Qinglong Hideout
are occupied by the Japanese one by one.
If we fight them blindly,
the result is very likely
just like those two villages.
Then...
So what we can do now
is to keep the strength of QinFo Ye Ravine.
When Wen Pei and the others bring the troop here,
No, when will the troop come?
I'm so worried.
Cui Wenkui.
How dare you come to see me?
Tell me.
Why did you leave your post?
It was an emergency that day.
I didn't have time to report to you.
so I brought my men there.
Because of your negligence,
because of your negligence.
Can you take the responsibility?
Yes.
I failed my duty.
So I came back this time
to make up for my mistake.
Make up for it?
Make yourself clear first.
Did you go to QinFo Ye Ravine these days?
Yes.
How dare you say that?
You're the Brigade Commander of the National Party.
is entangled with bandits.
Not only bandits, but also accomplices.
That woman named Chae Jin
Is she a commander or an accomplice?
Are you sure?
Cui Wenkui.
If I hadn't put in a good word for you,
you would have been killed.
Division Commander.
I will
I'll make it clear to you later.
The Japanese have taken down Shanzhou.
I know the terrain better.
How about this?
Give me some men and more guns.
I'll get it back.
Are you crazy?
How dare you hit me?
Cui Wenkui.
This is all I have.
If you don't get it all,
You don't want it, do you?
Don't mention it again.
Go back and reflect on yourself. Get out.
Get out, Division Commander.
Ms. Huo.
Bao.
Where are you going in a hurry?
No, I'm holding it in.
I'm going out to play with some pheasants.
Look, bad news is everywhere.
It's suffocating.
You brought so many things to play the pheasant?
No, why?
No?
Ms. Huo.
You brought so many weapons
you can kill a lot of demons, right?
You saw it through.
To be honest,
I'm going to beat the Japanese.
I can't let it go.
My brothers
were killed by the Japanese.
and killed Wang Shi Er.
Now the Japanese took over Qinglong Fortress.
Do you think I can sit still?
Ms. Huo,
I understand how you feel.
You heard
what I said to Eagle today.
This is not the time to be impulsive.
Colonel.
QinFo Ye Hill
is the most difficult
among the 18 swordsmen.
As for Huo Lang,
He's the Patriarch of QinFo Ye Hill.
Back then,
I wanted to make him work for me.
I didn't expect him to escape in Fuyang.
Didn't you subdue all swordsmen here?
Why is there another valley?
As far as I know,
the QinFo Ye Ravine
is in a remote valley.
the terrain is dangerous and peculiar.
I'm trying my best to find Huo Lang.
to find Huo Lang and Qin Fo Ye.
because Huo Lang has the third treasure map.
You're right.
If we don't get rid of these bandits,
we won't have a peaceful life.
Yes.
Although we occupy some villages,
some of the fortress have been empty.
and the swordsmen ran away.
They are fighting against us invisibly.
This is the hardest to deal with.
Is Qinglong Fortress alright?
Because of my plan,
so it’s very solid.
What kind of braid is in charge now?
That's why I can spare some time.
What about the QinFo Ye Ravine?
Bring him in.
What’s wrong with him?
He is the captain of Qinglong Camp.
Ask him to take us to QinFo Ye Hill.
Lord Tianyuan, I knew it.
There's nothing to hold you back.
Bao, look.
Who's here?
Aunt Shui, Uncle Liu.
Mr. Liu. Mr. Shui. Why are you here?
Brother.
Don't mention it.
Your Uncle Liu and I
are occupied by the devil.
So I discussed it with your Uncle Six.
Instead of wandering outside,
rather than wandering outside.
Yes.
Since my brother passed away,
the three swordsmen are getting worse.
My men came back from Qinglong Fortress
Qinglong Fortress is full of
in Qinglong Fortress.
He Xiaopian is so evil.
gave Qinglong Fortress
to Zheng Xiong Tian Yuan.
I was so blind.
When I think about this, I...
I really don't know
when I can take revenge.
Uncle Liu.
We will get even with him.
Here.
Eat something.
Where did you get it?
I bought it when I passed by the town.
Eat it while it's hot.
Here.
Half for each.
You haven't told me
what your name is.
You want to know?
Someone will call you Chae Jin.
and someone called you Cui Wenpei.
It makes me confused.
My real name is Choi Moon-bae.
Choi Moon-Kui is my brother.
Bao is the son of our former butler.
The three of us grew up together.
Later, something happened at home.
After my father died,
I arrived in Yan'an.
Then the organization sent me to Chongqing.
I joined the army.
My code name in the army is Dark Flower.
Cai is my name in Chongqing.
I was in the military for a while.
But I couldn't stand all the restrictions there.
I was sent back to the army.
Later, he was transferred to Shanzhou with the army.
My boss knew my resume,
he sent me to Qinglong Hideout as an undercover
as a spy.
I didn’t take the informant
but was turned against by Qinglong Fortress.
But I prefer the life of swordsmen.
What about the future?
I can't go back to Qinglong Fortress.
My Black Tiger Mountain
was blown up too.
Follow me to fight the devil.
You want to rebel me too?
Li San'er.
Can we not dig like this?
We're planting wheat. Dig deeper.
That's right. Isn't it good?
I didn't mean you, did I?
It's like digging a tree pit.
Do you hear me?
Dig deeper
Okay. I heard it.
Listen, everyone.
Keep digging this trench.
Not deep enough.
The kid’s cannons are too powerful.
The trench needs a whole person.
Do you hear me?
Dig carefully.
Dig for yourself.
It's good.
Stop.
What the hell is this place?
Looks like they're wandering around.
Why haven't we arrived yet?
You're lying to us.
I dare not.
Go through the forest
and go through another ditch.
Qin Fo Ye's ditch is complicated.
It's hard for outsiders to know the way in.
We're almost there.
Huo Lang is using the advantage of
of Qin Fo Ye
to be so arrogant.
This time,
we must take down his lair
so that he can never hide.
Let’s go.
Masters, look.
If the devil attacks our valley,
this is the only way.
Bao, that's enough.
I know where
I know what's going on with my eyes closed.
Stop looking.
Let's drink some wine.
Ms. Huo.
Let me see if there are any loopholes.
No bugs. What bugs?
Everyone.
Baoni.
Nini said
she has something to tell you.
Come to me.
I apologize on behalf of my father.
No.
No, girl.
Get up.
What are you doing?
Your aunts and uncles
will make you apologize.
Let me tell you.
Your father is your father.
From now on, you'll stay here
in Qin Fo Ye's place.
Do you hear me?
Hurry, help him up.
Get up.
Get up, kid.
You...
Get up.
Ms. Huo.
What's wrong?
Boss, bad news.
A group of demons came from the ditch.
How far?
One li away.
One li.
One.
Bao, I trust you now.
Give us some work.
One li.
We have a trench as cover.
It's not good for demons to use heavy weapons.
Our only shortage
is that there are less bullets than ghosts.
So we have to wait until the enemy gets close.
and finish them off.
You're right.
But we can't fight them head-on.
Water creditor, Master Liu.
You have to take the wounded in the village
women and children
Before the war starts,
before the war starts.
We haven't even started the war.
Why do you say that?
But it makes sense.
Liu, Master of Water.
Take them out of the cave behind the mountain.
there will be another mountain.
Enough, brother, let's go.
I'm not leaving.
The devil is at our door.
You want me to leave now?
No.
I'm not leaving.
If you don't leave, we have to take care of them.
You have to go.
I have to stay.
I have to avenge my brother and Liang.
Look at him.
Stop arguing.
What's wrong with you?
The war is coming.
Please follow the arrangement.
Master Liu,
We’ll meet demons on the way back.
It's also very dangerous.
So,
I'll leave their safety to you.
Let Liu go. I'm not leaving anyway.
Enough, stop talking.
The devil is at our door.
Let's go fight the enemy.
Let's split up. Hurry up.
Hurry up!
Get out of the cave.
Take good care of yourself.
Uncle Liu, I'll leave it to you.
Okay.
Baoni, come with me.
Sister.
Hurry!
Hurry.
Go.
Hurry up.
Keep up.
These bandits know tactics.
They dug up the trench.
It must be the accomplice Chae
Order the artillery to fight!
Yes
Get down.
Don't run around. Get down.
Eagle!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Hide.
Hurry. Hide.
Get down! Get down!
This is a brats bombing.
It'll be over soon.
Hide!
Get down! Don't run!
Get down!
Colonel.
Our firecrackers are fierce.
These Chinese
In front of the Japanese army,
in front of the Japanese army.
Order Team One, go!
Yes.
Hold on!
Don't let the Japanese come up.
Hurry, hold on.
Hold on!
Don't let the Japanese come up.
Yes.
Steamed buns.
Steamed buns. Take it, Ms. Huo.
This is the third treasure map.
Take Eagle and leave from the cave behind.
Uncle Erbai, hurry!
Let's go together.
Yes, we can't leave you alone.
Listen to me.
Look, the devil is coming.
You're his only blood.
I have to protect you.
Uncle Erbai
Bao.
Find the gold mine according to the treasure map.
Dig out gold, buy guns and cannons.
Hit the devil.
These two things are too important.
I don't trust others.
Please.
Ms. Huo,
You are the hero I met in this life.
A toast to you.
Fine.
Can I leave a name in your heart?
I accept it.
Let's go.
Uncle Erbai
Hurry up!
Uncle Erbai, Ms. Huo.
Little Japanese.
I'll kill you!
I live
for a quick death.
to kill more Japanese.
Even if I lose my head,
I'll make a new rule for you.
If anyone dares to rely on the Japanese,
I'll kill him first.
Ms. Huo.
We're not in the same field.
But I respect you as a hero.
What did you say?
You said I'm a hero.
Do you really think so?
Kids, do you hear me?
I'm a hero.
You are the hero I met in this life.
A toast to you.
Fine.
Can I leave a name in your heart?
I accept it.
Eagle.
Our lives
with his life.
Uncle Huo.
We're leaving.
Ms. Huo.
I'll remember
what you asked me to do.
Don't worry.
Stop!
Search!
The Japanese are here.
The town ahead is the woodshed.
If we can set a barrier here,
There should be garrisons in town.
But after this town, we'll reach the pool.
Stop!
Turn around.
Pass.
Good.
Miss Hua.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
Let's go.
You know how to operate?
When I was in the special training class,
in the special training class.
If the bullet is not removed in time,
your life will be in danger.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're safe.
Uncle Six!
Sister Eagle is back.
Uncle Liu.
Master Liu.
You're finally back.
I was so worried.
Are you all right?
Where are Second Brother and Master Water?
Where are they?
Here.
Slowly.
What medicine is this? It's so bitter.
The herbs I just picked
and some external
for you.
You know a lot.
I just know a little.
But you...
When I took the bullet for you,
you didn't even shout.
We've been through so much.
This is nothing.
Does your wound still hurt?
No.
You have a fever.
I'll get you some medicine.
I'm fine.
Wait for me here.
I'll be back soon.
You're a man.
He's the Second Brother Huo Lang I know.
He and Mr. Water.
didn’t embarrass our ancestors.
Master Shui is as good as men.
I must
revenge.
That's right.
We must take revenge.
But we can't act blindly.
Brother.
How should we
take revenge?
We need to be on the same boat
and focus to fight with the brats.
Now all the swordsmen
have escaped.
We have to find a way
to gather them around us.
With our own team,
I'm not afraid of him.
Although Shanzhou has fallen,
the Japanese army
in the Japanese army.
I've seen your barracks.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
As long as we have a gun,
we can fight them.
We can't fight big battles.
But we can kill a devil today.
Burn the warehouse tomorrow.
and the day after tomorrow.
We can't let the kids
live
in our land.
We have to make them defenseless.
I'm always worried.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Gather all the men on the mountain
and post the hero invitation.
Hero invitation?
Every mountain has its own rules.
Once the hero invitation is released, they will be summoned.
Last time,
was posted by my brother.
Back then,
a group of bandits came from other places.
My brother has gathered six hills
to fight against them.
This order
was passed down by Qinglong Fortress for generations.
I've been familiar since I was young.
Nini, get me some tissues.
What does this mean
It looks like Master's talisman.
This is the summoning order
of our 18 hills.
The level of a spell
is a hero card to face the enemy together.
What does that mean?
It's actually very simple. It's a riddle of words.
Try the first line.
Go to the ground.
Go to the pit.
All the brothers will gather here
they will gather here.
If you don't tell me,
if you don't tell me.
Write 100 copies of this post.
and paste them on every intersection.
Let's
wait here.
Do you have anti-inflammatory drugs?
What medicine?
Penicillin.
You want this medicine?
The Japanese didn't allow me to sell them, so I took them all away.
Japanese?
There are Japanese camps here.
Turn left ahead.
Thank you.
Captain Yoshida!
Captain Fujiwara reported that
they were attacked in the pool.
You're awake.
How do you feel? Feeling better?
Is the medicine not working?
Is this what you got last night?
Take your temperature.
Why did you take such a big risk?
Have you forgotten?
I want to revolt you.
If I don't save you,
the rebellion will fail.
Wen Pei.
I owe you my life.
I'll protect you from now on.
Your fever is gone.
By the way,
I went out to buy medicine last night
and found out what happened nearby.
There's a Japanese camp nearby.
It's in the town called Chai Bull.
a Japanese army stationed there.
I heard an important message there.
Our Eight Army is in the pool.
has been adapted to
Yuxi anti-Japanese guerrilla team.
The third and fourth teams.
Great.
Let's go to the pool.
No hurry.
We'll talk about it after you recover.
But the pool is so big.
Where can we find it?
Let's go to the county first.
and find the organization.
As long as we can contact them,
we can find the guerrilla team.
Report the situation in Shanzhou to the superiors.
According to the instructions,
according to the instructions.
Okay.
There are many people here.
It's easy to be found by swordsmen.
Let's go.
You haven't recovered yet.
Why don't we take a break?
It's okay.
It doesn't matter.
Let's sit over there.
Let's go.
Jishi Pharmacy.
Is this the place you mentioned?
Yes.
Isn't this where we meet?
Why is the door locked?
I think it's strange too.
This place must have been deserted for a long time.
Did the underground party organization
was destroyed too?
What do you mean?
This is the Eight-horn Lotus.
It's my code name.
They'll know when they see this.
Let's go.
Our invitation is really something.
A lot of people came in these days.
The swordsmen can't surrender to the demons.
Most of them are hiding.
They're waiting for us to summon them.
Just wait.
Someone will continue to vote.
Sure.
This brat wants to turn us
into their big rear.
You wish.
Guys.
Li is here.
How is the situation at the fortress?
Qinglong Fortress is no longer the original Qinglong Fortress.
Qinglong Fortress has become a Japanese fortress.
We stored a lot of weapons and ammunition in our fortress.
The surrounding walls are reinforced.
He Xiaopian.
What happened to He Xiaopian? Tell us.
He Xiaopian took his men
to Tianyuan Zhenghong.
He killed those who didn't surrender.
We have no choice.
Li.
This is your home.
Stay here
Uncle Liu, please arrange it.
Okay.
Li, come with me.
Bao.
I need to go back to Qinglong Fortress.
No.
That place
has become their camp.
I won't go from the front.
Did you forget?
There's a secret tunnel over there.
Uncle half a kilo is there too.
I have to go back and have a look.
Okay, don't go alone.
I'll go with you.
You can't leave.
Many brothers will come in these days.
You're the backbone here.
If you leave,
if you leave?
Since you've made up your mind,
no matter what I say, I can't stop you.
We've been through so much together.
You must know what to do now.
But you have to promise me
be careful.
I will.
Actor table.
Li Sheng Ye.
Liu Liwei.
and actors.
Li, Yu Hongda, Tian Guofeng, Gong, Fan, Cheng Kaiyan.
Su Tianhui, Yang Wanlin, Zhao Dongliang, Chen Yile. Wang Lusheng.
Yu Hongda Tian Guofeng Gong Fan Cheng Kaiyan
Yue, Wang, Yang Ziyi, Tian Chenzhe, Deng Kai Mei Liangdong.
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Sheng, Yang Haoyu, Zhou Chaoyang.
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Liu, Tong, Wang, Liu Jiawen, Sun, Jin. KUN.
Venus Feng Yonghao Wei Long Deng Bao Quan Wang Xiang
Liu Hongguo, Yang Chenglin, Liu Yinlong.
Li Jinyang, Zhang Jianing, Liu Rong Qi.
Wang Qingyu, Feng Qimeng, Chen Weipeng, Qiji, Wang Yan Qing.
Staff table.
Director team.
The production team.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
Cho Jeon-min.
Costume Team.
Costume team.
The dressing team.
Gong Hae Yeong.
Arts Team.
Zhang Zefeng.
Lei.
Props team.
Cui Guangzang.
Set team.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
The recording team.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Kang Jiping.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Rong Xi.
Chen Jianqi, Zhang Kunwu, Jin, Zhang Rong Li Zhang...
Ge Wenlong, Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang Zhang Jianping.
Yang Shuli, Chen Yongsheng, Liu Junfeng, Liu Fu Min
Cut.
Wei Meng.
behind the scenes, Shin Baejin.
[Late production]
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
dubber.
A dubber?
Music production.
Theme song, Hero.
Final production: Wang Chenyang.
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
Golden Golden Golden Golden Golden Valley.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
[Jangok Association, Shanzhou District]
Shanzhou District, Temple, Village Scenic Area.
The Villager Committee of Lingbao City
Maple Theatre, Mumei City.
The village committee of the old store in Shanzhou District.
Jiangzhou Zhou Jiajun Co., Ltd.
legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
The People's Government of Sanmen City
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
There are three branches in total.
The People's Government
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
Zhongtong County Commission.
The People's Government of Wenji County.
Henan Yunyang Liquor Co., Ltd.
The People's Government of YongChi County.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
[Sanmen Lanhu City Wetland Park]
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
Jiangjiang Dongyang Mai Jiang Culture Co., Ltd.
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Henan Provincial Film Association.
Shangjin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quanzhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
[Qijin Cultural Development Co., Ltd.]
Qijin (Quan Zhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Zhang Bing will be rewarded first.